IVETA ZELTINA



Address: Riga, Latvia Phone: +371 29215444

Email: iveta.zeltina@gmail.com

Languages

English – C1 Russian – C1 Latvian – native

Skills & Knowledge

Languages:

X++, C#, Python, JavaScript, Java, TypeScript, PHP, HTML5/CSS, C++

Technologies:

Microsoft Dynamics AX 2012, and Microsoft Dynamics AX 2009 Information Systems

Database-related languages:

SQL, MySQL

Operating Systems:

Windows, Linux

Frameworks:

Angular, Bootstrap, .NET

Tools:

Microsoft Power BI, Google Analytics, Google Ads, Facebook Ads Manager, WordPress, Drupal

Summary

Herewith I would like to offer my newly acquired knowledge and skills, as well as express my interest in the developer position with experience in X++.

Even though my prior work and educational experience does not completely relate to the area of programming and IT as such. However, I have now transitioned to this seemingly new area.

My initial interest for programming and software engineering has first develop during my prior working experience at Tilde company. This working experience gave me valuable insights into programming related work, as well as initiated a lasting interest in the IT industry.

I am currently working as a junior information systems developer with the X++ object-oriented language. I have become a part of the company MBIT that has been involved in the implementation and maintenance of the Microsoft Dynamics AX business management system in Latvia and abroad.

I am also currently studying at the Faculty of Computer Science of the University of Latvia. In addition to the academic program, I have accomplished courses to increase my knowledge in the chosen field.

I believe – the combination of my marketing background, academic engineering knowledge, and newly acquired programming experience would provide value for any team adding unique perspective, fresh look and understanding.

Education

• **Programming and Computer Network Administration**, Faculty of Computing, **University of Latvia**, 2020 – ...

Operating Systems; Computer Architecture and Computer Engineering Fundamentals; Web Technologies; Computer Networks and Insight into Industry; Software Testing; Algorithms and Programming; Data Structures and Algorithms; Mathematical Logic; Formal Grammars; Discrete Mathematics for Computing; Software Engineering; Probability Theory and Statistics; Automata Theory; Databases and Information Systems Fundamentals; Software Development Fundamentals, etc.

- Master's degree of Social Sciences, Faculty of Social Sciences, Political Science, Public Relations, University of Latvia
- Master's degree of Social Sciences, Faculty of Economics, International Economic Relations, Riga Technical university
- Bachelor's degree of Social Sciences, Faculty of Economics, International Economic Relations, Riga Technical university

Other Education

- Introduction to Networks (Cisco Networking Academy, netacad.com)
- Google IT Support (www.coursera.org)
- C++, JavaScript (<u>codecademy.com</u>)
- Microsoft Dynamics AX 2012 R3
 Data Selection and Manipulation (udemy.com)
- JavaScript, TypeScript, PHP (codelex.io)
- Introduction to Microsoft Power Platform (<u>balticinternships.eu</u>)
- HTML/CSS (khanacademy.org)
- Microsoft Dynamics AX 2012 R3 Form and Table Methods (udemy.com)
- Microsoft Dynamics AX 2012 R3 Programming (udemy.com)

IVETA ZELTINA

Skill Highlights

- Communication
- Collaboration
- Highly Organized
- Problem Solving
- Time Management
- Teamwork
- Attention to Details

Experience

05/2022 - ... - Junior AX Developer

MBIT, Microsoft Dynamics AX maintenance and service, automation of business processes, development of web solutions

• Creating customized software based on the Microsoft Dynamics AX framework, writing code using of X++ programming language, and managing the Dynamics AX system for a client, company.

11/2017 - 01/2019 - Head of Marketing

Towers Construction Management, real estate

 Developing marketing strategy for the mixed-used real estate project "Z-Towers", preparing creative concept and slogan, defining brand values, creating mission and vision of the company, selecting target markets and target audiences, choosing media channels and media titles, content marketing, PR, budgeting, supporting sales team, etc.

12/2016 – 10/2017 – Head of Marketing and Business Development Dienas Žurnāli, media, publishing house

Developing marketing strategy for the new magazine "JunioriTieto" launch in Finland: market and competition analysis, web page development, planning and implementation of digital campaign, developing creative ideas, cooperating with the partners (web designers, web page developers, media agency, digital agency).

01/2012 - 11/2016 - Baltic Marketing and Sales Manager

Tilde, IT, machine translation solutions, terminology tools and databases, mobile translation apps, and desktop proofing tools

 Developing marketing and sales strategy for B2B products (software, mobile apps, machine translation tools, desktop proofing tools, translation, and localization service, etc.), managing online and offline marketing campaigns, digital marketing (SMM, email marketing, display and search advertising, web analytics tools), PR communication, event marketing.

01/2007 - 12/2011 - Head of Marketing Department

Žurnāls Santa, media, publishing house

 Developing marketing strategy, providing efficient and successful operational work of the Marketing department.

01/2004 - 12/2006 - Project Director

Mediaedge:cia Latvia, media agency

 Providing client service in the Baltics, developing communication strategies, managing marketing campaigns (planning, estimating, coordinating), analysing results of campaigns.

03/2002 - 12/2003 - Project Manager

Media House, media agency

 Providing client service, developing communication strategies, managing marketing campaigns (planning, estimating, coordinating), analysing results of campaigns.